Folder inventory to the Marcus Raskin papers, 1952-2013 MS2297
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Paths, 1975-2004; Series 5
  - Study Groups and Community College, 1995; Series 5 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - PATHS 21st, undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - PATHS, undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Reconstructive, 2002; Series 5 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Levine- PATHS Project, December 13, 2004; Series 5 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Correspondence, 1961-2007; Series 6
  This series contains folders with a folder title of either correspondence or letters. It is a certainty that correspondence exists in other series and that the topics of folders in this series relate to topics in other series. Materials in this series are from 1961-2007.
  - Invitations, 1995; Series 6 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, 1994; Series 6 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, 1992-1993; Series 6 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, 1987-1998; Series 6 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Early Correspondence, 1974; Series 6 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence, 1977; Series 6 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence, 1995; Series 6 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Letters, 2001-2003; Series 6 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Bundy Correspondence, 1961; Series 6 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence, 2007; Series 6 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Important Letters, 2002-2007; Series 6 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence, 2000-2003; Series 6 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence, 1998-2006; Series 6 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Letters, 1996-2001; Series 6 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - From the Desk of Marcus Raskin, undated; Series 6 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Letters, 1969-2001; Series 6 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Letters, 1986-1992; Series 6 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence, 1996; Series 6 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence, 1999-2001; Series 6 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Letters, March 6, 2007; Series 6 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Chomsky Correspondence, 2004-2006; Series 6 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Correspondence, 1995-2006; Series 6 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - GW Memo, undated; Series 6 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Correspondence, 2007; Series 6 (Box 8, Folder 38)
- People, 1976-2007; Series 7
  This series contains material in which the folder title is the name of a person. It is likely that the materials in this series have topics that relate to topics in other series. Materials in this series are between 1976-2007.
  - Karl Hess, undated; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 39)
    This folder contains topics in policy research
  - Melman, 1990; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Boehm Proposals, 1994-2000; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Noam Chomsky, 1999-2000; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Dr. Frank Olsen, January 11, 1976; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Molly Andrews, 1993; Series 7 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Norman Birnbaum, September 1, 1995; Series 7 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Chomsky, 1995-1998; Series 7 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Chomsky Book, 1987-1998; Series 7 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Rod French, May 13, 2005; Series 7 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Gar Alperovitz, 1995; Series 7 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Bernard Rapoport, 1996; Series 7 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Bob Spero, 1994; Series 7 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Steve Trachtenberg, 1995; Series 7 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Margaret Wertheim, 1994; Series 7 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Laila Bernstein, 1999; Series 7 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Martin Garbus, undated; Series 7 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - G.A. Borgese and Paul M. Sweezy, undated; Series 7 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Alumni Awards- Baumbach, October 11, 2005; Series 7 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Jan Reiner, 2005; Series 7 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Norman Birnbawn, undated; Series 7 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Seymour Melman, undated; Series 7 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Michael Albert, April 9, 1993; Series 7 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Bundy, 1961-1963; Series 7 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Noam Chomsky, 2007; Series 7 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Arthur Waskow, 2004; Series 7 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    This folder contains a copy of Arthur Waskow's "New Freedom Seder."
  - Levine, undated; Series 7 (Box 9, Folder 22)
- Subject and research files, 1961-2008; Series 8
  This series contains various research files organized by subject between 1961-2008.
  - Catholic and Cold War, 1992; Series 8 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Soviet Conference, 1984; Series 8 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Vatican and Communism Research, 1978; Series 8 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Soviet Studies (Part 1), 1983-1984; Series 8 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Soviet Studies (Part 2), 1983-1984; Series 8 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Soviet Studies (Part 3), 1983-1984; Series 8 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Soviet Studies (Part 4), 1983-1984; Series 8 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Soviet Studies (Part 5), 1983-1984; Series 8 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Globalization/ New World Order, 1999; Series 8 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Higher Education, 21st Century, 1999; Series 8 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Transitional Institute 25th Anniversary, November 1999; Series 8 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Knowledge/ Culture, 1999; Series 8 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Democracy and Death of Soviet Union, undated; Series 8 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Middle East- Gulf, 1991; Series 8 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - United Nations, 1992; Series 8 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - CBO: National Security Needs, February 1990; Series 8 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Article on McGeorge Bundy, July 1969; Series 8 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Transcribed Interviews, undated; Series 8 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Reagan and National Security State, 1991; Series 8 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Raskin White House Memo, October 13, 1961; Series 8 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - National Security State, 1995-1996; Series 8 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - JFK, 1992; Series 8 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - JFK, 1992; Series 8 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Yugoslavia, undated; Series 8 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Fraud, Science, and Reconstruction, 1988-1991; Series 8 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Affirmative Action, 1989-1992; Series 8 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Congressional Record: Anti- terrorism Bill, 1995; Series 8 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Employment, undated; Series 8 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Electoral Reform, 1994-1997; Series 8 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - D.C., 1993-1996; Series 8 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - 1994 Election, Series 8 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - D.C., 1996; Series 8 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Education, 1995; Series 8 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Official Accountability Act, 1976; Series 8 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Official Accountability, 1993; Series 8 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Peace, 1994; Series 8 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Racism, 1982; Series 8 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Schools, undated; Series 8 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Taxes, 1991-1992; Series 8 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - The Other Economic Summit, 1994; Series 8 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Violence, 1997; Series 8 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - American Requiem, undated; Series 8 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Clinton, undated; Series 8 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Crime Bill, 1994-1995; Series 8 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Cuba, 1993; Series 8 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Death of The Soviet Union (Original), 1993; Series 8 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Hague Peace Initiative, 1994; Series 8 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Haiti, 1994; Series 8 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Bill Cannon: Heathcare, January 1995; Series 8 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Joseph of the Bible, May 3, 1994; Series 8 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Cvijeto Job, 1993; Series 8 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Labor, 1994-1996; Series 8 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Vietnam, undated; Series 8 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Institute for Jewish Public Affairs Proposal, September 1989; Series 8 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - ISIS, 1992-1995; Series 8 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - NYT Magazine: Bob Moses, 1993; Series 8 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Peace Action Ed. Fund, 1993-1995; Series 8 (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Social Project, 1977; Series 8 (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Securing Democracy, 1993; Series 8 (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - Human Genome Project and Related, 1993-1994; Series 8 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Health, 1977-1992; Series 8 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Dictatorship- Kirkpatrick, 2006; Series 8 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Richard Norman- Terrorism, December 1, 2001; Series 8 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Drugs and Personality, July 28, 2006; Series 8 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Peace Action, February 22, 2006; Series 8 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Reconstruction Program, undated; Series 8 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Blacks in Government (B.I.G.), January 16, 2005; Series 8 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Technological Bases for Social Change, undated; Series 8 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Passion for War, February 19, 2004; Series 8 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Flavors of American War, undated; Series 8 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Freedom and Security Class, 2004; Series 8 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - GW Exporting Thought, undated; Series 8 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Stonewall, undated; Series 8 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Cold War, 2002; Series 8 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Iraq, 1996-2006; Series 8 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Impeachment Project, 2005; Series 8 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - MacArthur Foundation, September 17, 2001; Series 8 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Terrorism, undated; Series 8 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Cities for Progress, 2006; Series 8 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Quantum Brain, 1994; Series 8 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - War and Military Crimes, undated; Series 8 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Unemployment Insurance Company, undated; Series 8 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Fundraising, 2004; Series 8 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - National Security (Dwyer), 2001-2003; Series 8 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - National Security, 1994-2002; Series 8 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - National Security #2, 2005; Series 8 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Patriot Act, undated; Series 8 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Philosophy of Political and Social Fasions, 2005; Series 8 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Pres. Disrespect, undated; Series 8 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Questions Regarding Iraq, undated; Series 8 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Presidential Quotes, undated; Series 8 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - The Rebel Gin, undated; Series 8 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - National Security Strategy Excercise- ICAF, 2003; Series 8 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - The Ludlow Massacre, undated; Series 8 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Propaganda by the Deed, undated; Series 8 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Democracy, undated; Series 8 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Current, 2006; Series 8 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Iraq/ Iran, 2007; Series 8 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Nation Linginam, undated; Series 8 (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Science, undated; Series 8 (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Sociology of Science, 2006- 2007; Series 8 (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - University, 2001; Series 8 (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - United Nations, undated; Series 8 (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - Briefing Papers of U.S./ Soviet Discussion, 1975-1985; Series 8 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Atomic Bomb, undated; Series 8 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Russia, undated; Series 8 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Democracy and Death of the Soviet Union, undated; Series 8 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Nuremberg, 1990-1995; Series 8 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Disarmament, 1985- 1993; Series 8 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Abolishing Nuclear Weapons, 1995; Series 8 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - General Disarmament and Common Security and Non- Proliferation, 1994; Series 8 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Disarmament, 1969-1995; Series 8 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - National Security State Book, 1977; Series 8 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - National Security State, 1975-1993; Series 8 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - National Security State, 1990; Series 8 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Military Arms and Disarmament, 1978-1989; Series 8 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - North-South, 1992; Series 8 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Documents on Disarmament, 1989-1991; Series 8 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Bulletin of the Atomic Scientists, 1982-1983; Series 8 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - UNESCO: Arms Control, 1991; Series 8 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Nuclear Experimentation on Civilians, 1952; Series 8 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Constitutional Constraints: The War Clause, 1993; Series 8 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Cost of Nuclear Weapons, 1951-1995; Series 8 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Cannon- Budget, 1990; Series 8 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - MacArthur Foundation, March 27, 1996; Series 8 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Education, 1991-1995; Series 8 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Fluxioms, 1991-1996; Series 8 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Raskin Notes, undated; Series 8 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Dark Times, April 30, 2004; Series 8 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Atomic Bomb, 2006; Series 8 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Baumbach, undated; Series 8 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Birth of Israel, 1946-2003; Series 8 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Impeachment, 2005; Series 8 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - National Security State, undated; Series 8 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Human Rights, 2005-2007; Series 8 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - U.S. Intervention in Afghanistan, July 15, 2004; Series 8 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Race and Reconstruction, 2007; Series 8 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Religion, undated; Series 8 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Middle East: Israel and Palestine, 1998; Series 8 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Nuclear, 2007; Series 8 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Antioch College, 2007; Series 8 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Samuel Rubin Foundation, 2003-2005; Series 8 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Impeachment, 2007; Series 8 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Men and Women in Dark Places (Melman), 2005; Series 8 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Iraq, 2007; Series 8 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Vulture Fund, 2007; Series 8 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - JFK Lib, 1962-1963; Series 8 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Reconstructive Knowledge, undated; Series 8 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Climate Change, undated; Series 8 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Personal Decision Making (Case Studies), 2007; Series 8 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Presidential Powers/ Bush, undated; Series 8 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - National Security State and Globalization, undated; Series 8 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - National Security Strategy Excercise, undated; Series 8 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Economic Democracy, 2008; Series 8 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - March Towards Democracy and Beyond, undated; Series 8 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Impeachment, undated; Series 8 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Various Research Materials, 2007-2008; Series 8 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - American Politics- Clinton, undated; Series 8 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Senate Committee on Finance, 1990; Series 8 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Pragmatism, June 1996; Series 8 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Education: Paths of Liberation, 2000; Series 8 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Gandhi Economics, undated; Series 8 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Inside and Outside, undated; Series 8 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Nuremberg- Marcus Raskin, Spring 1971; Series 8 (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Contextuality: Mapping the Social and Decision Processes, undated; Series 8 (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Research Prospects for Liberalism, 1993-2002; Series 8 (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - Economics of Democracy, February 18, 1998; Series 8 (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - Global Wars, undated; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Political- Nader Campaign, undated; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Logic/ Reconstruction- Moses (Part 1 of 2), 1986; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Logic/ Reconstruction- Moses (Part 2 of 2), 1986; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - To the Progressive Caucus, July 4, 2005; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - "From Mad Jack", 1996-2003; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Economic Goals and Intergovernmental Policy, 1984-1998; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Iraq, 2003-2008; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Impeachment, 2005; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Raskin White House Files, undated; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Barbara Lee- Congress, October 2003; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Reconstruction PPOL, undated; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Ohio Election- Convers Report, 2004; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Rubin Foundation, 2001-2006; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Presidents, undated; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Reference Materials, 1991; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Great Law of Peace, undated; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Education, 1998; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - DC2000: District of Columbia, 1990-1991; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Balkans, 1999; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Academic Freedom and Governance, 1998-1999; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Mass Culture, undated; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - FBI versus Marcus Raskin, 1973-1990; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Defense and National Security, 1950-1985; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Whitney Museum/ Kienholz, 1995; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Various Research Materials, 1976-2001; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 26)
- The Liberal Project, 1952-2013; Series 9
  Arrangement
  This series contains three subseries: People, correspondence, research and writings, and the Liberal Project.
  This series includes items that were donated in 2014 and spans from 1952-2013, with the bulk of the material coming from 1959-1962. It includes correspondence, memos, press releases, essays, and articles related to the Liberal Project, of which Marcus Raskin was the secretary. The Liberal Project started in the late 1950s-early 1960s and was comprised of scholars, scientists and experts, and political leaders who sought to redefine the term liberalism and better apply it to current events. Topics addressed within the project included International Relations, Law and the Judiciary, Education, Science and Culture, Economic and Industrial Affairs, and Defense Policy. The Liberal Project also published many of their essays in a 1962 book, "The Liberal Papers." This series includes files on the various members of the Liberal Project as well. These files consist of correspondence and essays written by the members.
  Finally, this series contains general correspondence, works written and collected by Marcus Raskin on the topics listed above for the Liberal Project, and articles and programs for various lectures and conferences he attended. It also includes organized files with outlines of Raskin's correspondence and memos in the Wisconsin History folders. This series contains materials associated with the Liberal Project between 1952 and 2013.
  - People, 1959-1962; Series 9 Subseries 1
    This subseries contains files on the various members of the Liberal Project and spans from 1959-1962. These files include correspondence and essays written by the members.
    - Edwards, Corwin - Economic Policy, 1959-1960; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Eichelberger, Clark - Defense, 1960; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Ewing, Oscar R. - Economic, 1959-1960; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Franklin, John Hope - Law and the Judiciary, 1959-1960; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Fromm, Erich - Philosophic, 1959-1960; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Gass, Oscar, 1960-1961; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Goodman, Paul - Education and Culture, 1959-1960; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Haber, David - Racial Equality and the Law, 1960; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Hughes, H. Stuart - Foreign Policy, 1959-1962; Sreies 9 Subseries 1 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Hutchins, Robert M. - Philosophic, 1959-1960; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Johnson, Byron - Congressional, 1959-1960; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Kahler, Erich - Philosophic, 1959-1960; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Kasem, George - Congressional, 1959-1960; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Kowalski, Frank - Congressional, 1959-1960; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Lasswell, Harold D. - Philosophic, 1959-1960; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Liveright, Alexander A. - Education and Culture, 1959-1960; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Maccoby, Michael, 1960-1961; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - McDougal, Myres - Space Law, 1960; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - McGovern, George - Congressional, 1959-1961; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Metcalf, Lee - Congressional, 1960; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Meyer, William - Congressional, 1959-1960; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Miller, Clem - Congressional, 1959-1960; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Millis, Walter - Defense, 1959-1961; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Northrop, F.S.C. - Philosophic, 1959; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Porter, Charles O. - Congressional, 1959-1960; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Rabinowitch, Eugene - Education and Culture, 1959-1960; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - Riesman, David - Philosophic, 1959-1961; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - Rodell, Fred - Legal Rights, 1960; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Roosevelt, James - Congressional, 1960-1961; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Rostow, Walt Whitman - Foreign, 1959-1960; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Schwartz, Bernard - Law and Judiciary, 1959-1960; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Shils, Edward A. - Philosophic, 1959-1960; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Smyth, Henry - Education and Culture, 1959-1960; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Smythe, Dallas, 1959-1961; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Tannenbaum, Frank - Latin-Amer. Policy, 1960; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Taylor, Harold - Education and Culture, 1959-1960; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Wallerstein, Immanuel M. - Foreign, 1959-1961; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Albertson, Maurice, 1961; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Arendt, Hannah - Philosophic, 1959-1960; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Arnold, Thurman - Law and the Judiciary, 1959-1960; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Atlee, John S., 1960-1961; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Ayres, Clarence - Economic, 1959-1960; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Barth, Alan - Law and Judiciary, 1959; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Bell, Daniel - Economic Policy, 1959-1960; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Benoit, Emile, 1961; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Blough, Roy - Economic, 1959-1960; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Blum, Walter-Taxation, 1960; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Bohan, Merwin - Foreign, 1959-1960; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Boulding, Kenneth Ewart - Economic, 1959-1961; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Bowles, Chester - Congressional, 1959; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Brademas, John - Congressional, 1959; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - Cahn, Edmond - Law and Judiciary, 1959-1960; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - Chase, Stuart - Economic Policy, 1960; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - Cochrane, Willard - Economic, 1959-1960; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Cogley, John - Law and Judiciary, 1959-1960; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - Davis, Kingsley - Foreign Policy, 1960; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - Dean, Vera Micheles - Foreign Policy, 1959-1961; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - Denney, Reuel - Education and Culture, 1960; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - Dienstfrey, Harris, 1960; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence, research and writings, 1954-2013; Series 9 Subseries 2